airtame.com 2019-01-29

# Privacy Policy – Airtame

## Section 1 – What data do we collect and why?

### Purchase

When you purchase something from our store, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information, such as your name, address, telephone number and email address. As well as online identifiers, such as the internet protocol (IP), browser and operating system.

We collect the above mentioned data points in order to provide you with essential functionality of our third-party e-commerce platform. Additionally, we use your purchasing history in automated decision-making activities in order to provide you with the most relevant and best content and services possible.

## Marketing offers

When signing up for any of our newsletter and other email submission offers we collect the personal information defined in the submission form, such as your name, telephone number and email address. As well as online identifiers, such as the internet protocol (IP), browser and operating system.

We collect the above mentioned data points in order to provide you with essential functionality of our service and to improve such. Additionally, we use your online behaviour in profiling activities in order to provide you with the most relevant and best content and services possible.

## Account creation on Airtame Cloud

When signing up for an account for our remote management platform (“Airtame Cloud”) we collect the personal information email address. As well as online identifiers, such as the internet protocol (IP), browser and operating system.

We collect the above mentioned data points in order to provide you with essential functionality of our service and to improve such. Additionally, we use your online behaviour in profiling activities in order to provide you with the most relevant and best content and services possible.

## Information from Integrated Sign-On Services

If you decide to register through or otherwise grant access to a third-party integrated service (what we call an “Integrated Service”), such as Google or similar single sign-on service, Airtame Aps may also collect Personal Information that is already associated with your Integrated Service account. You may also have the option of sharing additional information with Airtame Aps through an Integrated Service, as controlled through your settings on that Integrated Service. If you choose to provide such information, during registration or otherwise, Airtame Aps will treat the information as Personal Information and will use it in the ways described in our Terms of Service.

## Internal analytics, product health and improvement

When using our devices we collect online identifiers, such as the internet protocol (IP), browser and operating system.

We collect the above mentioned data points in order to provide you with essential functionality of our service and to improve such.

## Booking calls with Airtame

When booking a call with an Airtame employee through our third-party service we collect the personal information defined in the submission form, such as your name, telephone number and email address. As well as online identifiers, such as the internet protocol (IP), browser and operating system.

We collect the above mentioned data points in order to provide you with essential functionality of our service and to improve such. Additionally, we use your online behaviour in profiling activities in order to provide you with the most relevant and best content and services possible.

## Email marketing

Any submission of email with us constitutes that you expressly agree to receive promotional content from Airtame, news about our product and its development, as well as relevant tips and insights by mail or email, from time to time. You will also be given an option to opt out of receiving our promotional materials.

Our mailing program allows us to see when you open our email and click and we use that information for automated decision making, profiling and performance monitoring and improvements.

## Section 2 – Consent

## How do you get my consent?

Website – If you choose to use the website, you indicate your consent to our use of the cookies any information about you that we collect using these cookies. If you do not consent to the use of these technologies, please do not use the website. Learn more about our Cookie Policy (“Cookie Policy”).

Purchases – When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.

Marketing – If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will ask you directly for your expressed consent. All of our marketing communications are on a opt-in basis and require a explicit action of you.

## How do I withdraw my consent?

If after you opt-in you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at hello@airtame.com. To stop receiving our Newsletter just use the Unsubscribe button in the Newsletter from Airtame you have received, and in order to object to the use of cookies please follow the instruction at the bottom of our Cookie Policy to suppress cookies in your respective browser or please refrain from using the website.

## Section 3 – Data subject rights of access

We have outlined the data subject rights that apply to Airtame’s data subjects below. If you at anytime, would like to exercise any of the below outlined rights or have questions regarding them please contact us at data@airtame.com.

## Right of access

The controller shall take appropriate measures to provide any information relating to processing to the data subject in a concise, transparent, intelligible and easily accessible form, using clear and plain language, in particular for any information addressed specifically to a child.

## Right to erasure and to be forgotten

The data subject shall have the right to obtain from the controller the erasure of personal data concerning their without undue delay, unless otherwise required by law.

## Right to rectification

The data subject has the right to have inaccurate personal data rectified. An individual may also be able to have incomplete personal data completed – although this will depend on the purposes for the processing. This may involve providing a supplementary statement to the incomplete data.

## Right to data portability

The data subject has the right to receive personal data they have provided to a controller in a structured, commonly used and machine readable format. It also gives them the right to request that a controller transmits this data directly to another controller.

## Right to restrict processing

The data subject has a right to restrict the processing of any personal data stored by Airtame. In most cases, this cannot be an indefinite restriction, only for a period of time.

## Disclaimer

All of these rights include more detailed stipulations, which need to be assessed before complying with any requests based on the above mentioned rights. Additionally, we reserve the right to exercise reasonable measures to verify the identity of any data subject putting forward requests based on the above rights. This is to ensure the security of our existing data subjects and to minimize the risk of fraudulent behaviours. More information on the aforementioned stipulations can be found here (“EU GDPR information portal”).

## Section 4 – Disclosure

We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.

## Section 5 – Shopify

Our store is hosted on Shopify Inc. They provide us with the online e-commerce platform that allows us to sell our products and services to you. Your data is stored through Shopify’s data storage, databases and the general Shopify application. They store your data on a secure server behind a firewall.

## Payment

If you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, then Shopify stores your credit card data. It is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as it is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted.

All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover.

PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers. For more insight, you may also want to read Shopify’s Terms of Service or Privacy Statement.

## Section 6 – Third-party services

In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us. However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.

For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers. In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located. As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.

Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.

## Links

When you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.

## Section 7 – Security

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed. If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption. Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.

## Section 8 – Cookies

We use cookies to personalise content and ads, to provide social media features and to analyse our traffic. We also share information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners who may combine it with other information that you’ve provided to them or that they’ve collected from your use of their services. We urge you to consult our Cookie Policy for further information.

## Section 9 – Age of consent

By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.

## Section 10 – Changes to this privacy policy

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it. If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.

## Questions and contact information

If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information, see the bottom of this page for our contact information.
